IVAN JOSE MIRANDA RAMIREZ

Web Developer

CONTACT

+1 438-365-1908

✓ ivanjose_04@hotmail.com

Github

Portfolio

EDUCATION

2023 - 2024 TECCART (MONTREAL)

· Web and mobile programming

2015 - 2020 UAC (COLOMBIA)

• Industrial Engineering

SKILLS

- Web Design
- · Front-end coding
- Database Management
- User Interface/User Experience
- · Design Thinking
- Full Stack Web and Multi-platform
 Mobile App Development

LANGUAGES

English: Fluent French: Fluent

• Spanish: Native

PROFILE SUMMARY

Web developer with solid competencies in web design, front-end coding, knowledge of SQL and NoSQL databases, and experience as a QA Analyst. I have a rapid learning ability that allows me to master new technologies to solve complex problems and improve user experience through Design Thinking. I value teamwork and collaborate in different environments to achieve goals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DevXpress

Intern

May 2024 - July 2024

- Built websites with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and PHP.
- Integrated dynamic features, ensured responsive design, and optimized web performance.
- Used GitHub for version control, deployed sites, and created a translation script with YAML, Bash, and Python.

SaravalenciaEstudio

April 2024 - Current

Freelance

- Developed a custom e-commerce site using WordPress and WooCommerce, including a booking system for appointments and video calls.
- Designed user-friendly interfaces, integrated payment gateways, and implemented SEO best practices.
- Coordinated with the client, provided updates, and conducted thorough testing for a seamless user experience.

Miranetworks

December 2021 - October 2022

QA Analyst & Web Master

- Prepared detailed reports on web and mobile app functionality during collaboration with Ab InBev.
- Oversaw project development, ensuring smooth progression and CMS-based adjustments.
- Developed Cypress automation scripts to enhance and streamline website functionalities.